Many of the distributions you use in data science are not discrete binomial, and
許多分佈(distribition)你在數據科學中使用的不是離散的二項式(binomial)，
instead are continues where the value of the given observation isn't
而是連續的，其中的觀察值
a category like heads or tails, but can be represented by a real number.
不是頭或尾，而可以表示為實數。
It's common to then graph these distributions when talking about them,
在討論這些分佈時，通常會將這些分佈進行圖形化，
where the x axis is the value of the observation and
其中x軸是觀察值，
the y axis represents the probability that a given observation will occur.
y軸代表給定的觀察發生的概率。
If all numbers are equally likely to be drawn when you sample from it,
如果所有的數字有同樣的可能性被抽選，當取樣時，
this should be graphed as a flat horizontal line.
應將其畫成水平線。
And this flat line is actually called the uniform distribution.
而這條平線實際上被稱為均勻(uniform)分佈。
There are few other distributions that get a lot more interesting.
還有其他幾個更有趣的分佈。
Let's take the normal distribution which is also called Gaussian Distribution or
我們來看一下常態(normal)分佈，也稱為高斯(Gaussian)分佈，
sometimes, a Bell Curve.
有時，一個鐘形(bell)曲線。
This distribution looks like a hump where the number which has
該分佈看起來像一個駝峰，其中數字
the highest probability of being drawn is a zero, and
繪製在概率最高的地方為零，
there are two decreasing curves on either side of the X axis.
並且有兩個遞減曲線在X軸的任一側上。
One of the properties of this distribution is that the mean is zero,
這種分佈的特徵之一是平均值(mean)為零，
not the two curves on either side are symmetric.
兩邊的兩條曲線是對稱的。
I want to introduce you to the term expected value.
我想向你介紹一下期望(expected)值。
I think that most of us are familiar with the mean is the sum of all the values
我認為我們大多數人都熟悉的平均值是，所有值的總和
divided by the total number of values.
除以值的總數量。
Calculating a mean values are computational process, and
計算平均值是一個計算過程，
it takes place by looking at samples from distribution.
它通過查看樣本的分佈來進行。
For instance rolling a die three times might give you 1,
例如擲骰子三次，可能會給你的數位1，
2 and 6, the mean value is then 4.5.
2和6，平均值是4.5。
The expected value is the probability from the underlying distribution is
預期值是從基本的分佈的概率。它是
what would be the mean of a die roll if we did an infinite number of rolls.
骰子點數的平均值，如果我們做了無限數次的擲骰子。
The result is 3.5 since each face of the die is equally likely to appear.
結果是3.5，因為骰子的每個面都同樣可能出現。
Thus the expected value is 3.5,
因此預期值是3.5，
while the mean value depends upon the samples that we've taken, and
雖然平均值取決於我們已經採取的樣本，它
converges to the expected value given a sufficiently large sample set.
將匯集到預期值，如果有一個足夠大的樣本集。
We'll talk more about expected values in course three.
我們將在第三課中詳細討論預期值。
A second property
第二個屬性
is that the variance of the distribution can be described in a certain way.
是分佈的變異數(variance)可以用某種方式來描述。
Variance is a measure of how badly values of samples are spread out from the mean.
變異數是衡量樣本值從平均值擴散攤開多寬的度量。
Let's get a little bit more formal about five different characteristics of
讓我們更加正式地分析五種不同的特徵
distributions.
在分佈(distribution)上。
First, we can talk about the distribution central tendency,
首先，我們可以談論分佈的中心集中趨勢，
and the measures we would use for this are mode, median, or mean.
我們為此使用的衡量是，模式(mode),中位數(median)或平均值(mean)。
This characteristic is really about where the bulk of probability
這一特性實際上是:大部分的概率是在哪裡的
is in the distribution..
分佈(distribution)上。
We can also talk about the variability in the distribution.
我們也可以談在分佈變異性。
There are a couple of ways we can speak of this.
有幾種方法我們可以說這個。
The standard deviation is one, the interquartile range is another.
標準差(Standard deviation)是一個，四分之一的範圍(interquartile range)是另一個。
The standard deviation is simply a measure of how different each item,
標準差衡量我們樣本中每個項目
in our sample, is from the mean.
與平均值的差異程度。
Here's the formula for standard deviation.
這裡是標準差的計算公式。
It might look a little more intimidating than it actually is.
它可能看起來比它實際上更加嚇人
Let's just walk through how we would write this up.
讓我們來看看我們如何寫這個。
Let's draw 1,000 samples from a normal distribution with
我們從正態分佈中抽取1000個樣本，
an expected value of 0.75 and a standard deviation of 1.
預期值為0.75，標準偏差為1.
Then we calculate the actual mean using NumPy's mean feature.
然後使用NumPy的mean特徵計算實際平均值。
The part inside the summation says xi- x bar.
總結中的部分表示xi-xbar。
Xi is the current item in the list and x bar is the mean.
Xi是列表中的當前項，xbar是平均值。
So we calculate the difference, then we square the result,
所以我們計算差額，然後我們平方該結果，
then we sum all of these.
然後我們總和所有這些。
This might be a reasonable place to use a map and apply a lambda to calculate
這可能是合理的地方來使用map，並應用lambda來計算
the differences between the mean and the measured value.
平均值和測量樣本值之間的差異，
Then to convert this back to a list, so NumPy can use it.
然後將其轉換回列表，因此NumPy可以使用它。
Now we just have to square each value, sum them together, and take the square root.
現在我們只需要對每個值進行平方，將它們相加在一起，並取平方根。
So that's the size of our standard deviation.
這就是我們的標準差的大小。
It covers roughly 68% of the area around the mean,
它占地大約68%平均值的周圍地區，
split evenly around the side of the mean.
均勻分佈在平均值的兩邊。
Now we don't normally have to do all this work ourselves, but
現在，我們通常不需要自己做所有這些工作，但
I wanted to show you how you can sample from the distribution,
是我想向你展示如何從分佈中進行抽樣，
create a precise programmatic description of a formula, and apply it to your data.
創建一個公式的精確程式描述，並將其應用於你的數據。
But for standard deviation, which is just one particular measure of variability,
但是對於標準差，這只是一個特定的變量度量，
NumPy has a built-in function that you can apply, called STD.
NumPy具有可以應用的內置函數，稱為std。
There's a couple more measures of distribution that are interesting to
還有更多一些對分佈的衡量是值得來
talk about.
談論的。
One of these is the shape of the tales of the distribution and
其中之一是分佈的尾巴的形狀，
this is called the kurtosis.
這被稱為峰度(kurtosis)。
We can measure the kurtosis using the statistics functions in the SciPy package.
我們可以測量峰度(kurtosis)使用SciPy 套裝軟體中的統計函數。
A negative value means the curve is slightly more flat
負值表示曲線稍微更平坦，
than a normal distribution, and a positive value means the curve is
相比於正態分佈(normalnbspdistribution)，正值表示曲線
slightly more peaky than a normal distribution.
比正態分佈略高。
Remember that we aren't measuring the kurtosis of the distribution per se, but
記住，我們不是測量分佈本身的峰度，而是
of the thousand values which we sampled out of the distribution.
我們從分佈中抽取出來的數千個值。
This is a sublet but important distinction.
這是一個微妙但重要的區別。
We could also move out of the normal distributions and
我們也可以移動正態分佈，
push the peak of the curve one way or the other.
推動曲線的峰值向左或者向右。
And this is called the skew.
這就是所謂的偏斜(skew)。
If we test our current sample data, we see that there isn't much of a skew.
如果我們測試我們現在的樣本數據，我們看到沒有太多的偏差(skew)。
Let's switch distributions and take a look at a distribution called the Chi Squared
我們來轉換分佈，看看一種分佈叫做Chi Squared分佈，
distribution, which is also quite commonly used in statistic.
這個分佈在統計學中也很常用。
The Chi Squared Distribution has only one parameter called the degrees of freedom.
Chi Squared分佈只有一個參數稱為自由度(degree of freedom)。
The degrees of freedom is closely related to the number of samples that you take
自由度與你中獲取的樣本數量密切相關，
from a normal population.
從標準的樣本群體，
It's important for significance testing.
在顯著性的測試很重要。
But what I would like you to observe, is that as the degrees of freedom increases,
但是，我想要觀察的是，隨著自由度的增加，
the shape of the Chi Squared distribution changes.
Chi Squared分佈的形狀發生變化。
In particular, the skew to the left begins to move towards the center.
特別地，左邊的偏斜開始向中心移動。
We can observe this through simulation.
我們可以通過模擬來觀察。
First we'll sample 1,000 values from a Chi Squared distribution with degrees of
首先，我們將從Chi Squared分佈中挑選1,000個值，
freedom 2.
用自由度2。
Now we can see that the skew is quite large.
現在我們可以看到，偏差(skew)是相當大的。
Now if we re-sample changing degrees of freedom to 5.
現在，如果我們重新採樣，把自由度改變為5。
We see that the skew has decreased significantly.
我們看到偏差顯著下降。
We can actually plot this right in the Jupiter notebook.
我們實際上可以在Jupyter筆記本中繪製這個。
I'm not going to talk much about the library we're using here for plotting,
我不會談論太多關於我們這裡用於繪圖的程式庫，
because that's the topic of the next course.
因為這是下一課程的主題。
But you can see a histogram with our plot with the two degrees of freedom is skewed
但是你可以看到一個histogram，我們兩個自由度的曲線，
much further to the left,
非常向左偏斜，
while our plot with the five degrees of freedom is not as highly skewed.
而我們五個自由度的曲線並沒有那麼高度的偏斜。
I could encourage you as always to play with this notebook and
我會像往常一樣鼓勵你在這筆記本練習，
change the parameters and
改變參數，
see how the degrees of freedom changes the skew of the distribution.
看看自由度如何改變分佈的偏差(skew)。
The last aspect of distributions that I want to talk about is the modality.
我想討論分佈的最後一個是模式(modality)。
So far, all of the distributions I've shown have a single high point, a peak.
到目前為止，我已經展示的分佈都有一個高點，一個高峰。
But what if we have multiple peaks?
但是如果我們有多個峰值呢？
This distribution has two high points, so we call it bimodal.
這個分佈有兩個高點，所以我們稱之為雙峰(bimodal)。
These are really interesting distributions and happen regularly in data mining.
這些是真正有趣的分佈，並在數據挖掘中經常發生。
We're going to talk a bit more about them in course three.
我們將在第三個課程中談更多關於他們，
But a useful insight is that we can actually model these using
但有用的理解是，我們其實可以模仿這些使用
two normal distributions with different parameters.
兩個帶有不同參數的正常分佈。
These are called Gaussian Mixture Models and
這些被稱為高斯混合(Gaussian Mixture)模型，
are particularly useful when clustering data.
在聚類(clustering)數據時特別有用。
Well, this has been a long lecture but I think it can be tough to chop
好的，這一直是漫長的課堂，但我認為它很難分開
up a discussion of distributions and still get the main points across.
分佈來討論，而仍然瞭解主要的觀點。
Remember that a distribution is just a shape that describes the probability
請記住，分佈是只是一個形狀，描述它的概率
of a value being pulled when we sample a population.
用我們抽取的群體樣本的值。
And NumPy and SciPy each have a number of different distributions built in for
NumPy和SciPy各有一些不同的分佈內置函數
us to be able to sample from.
讓我們能夠從中取樣。
The last point I want to leave you with here is a reference.
最後一點我想離開你這裡的是一個參考書，
If you find this way of exploring statistics interesting.
如果你發現這種方式來探索統計很有趣。
Alan Downey wrote a nice book called Think Stats by the publisher O'Reilly.
艾倫·唐尼（Alan Downey）寫了一本名叫“Think stats”由出版社O'Reilly的書。
I think he does a really nice job of teaching how to think about statistics
我覺得他真的做的很好來教導如何思考有關統計
from a programming perspective.
從程式設計的角度來看。
One where you write the functions behind the statistical methods.
一個你編寫功能，應用背後的統計方法。
It's not really a reference book, but
這不是一本參考書，但
it's an interesting way to approach learning the fundamentals of statistics.
它是一個有趣的方式來學習統計的基礎知識。
Allen even has a free copy of this book available on his website in PDF format
Allen甚至在他的網站上以PDF格式提供這本書的免費副本，
and, of course, all of the code is done in Python.
當然所有的程式都是用Python完成的。